Guide to the Women-In-Action for the Prevention of Violence and Its Causes, Inc. Durham Chapter records, 1968-1998
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (1996-0164), 1980s-1990s, (13 boxes)
  Administrative files from the 1980s-1990s, which include office files, financial records, project files, newsletters, and awards ceremonies. Contains some photographs.
  - Administrative files (Box 1)
  - Administrative files, writings and speeches, subcommittees, miscellaneous, and clippings (Box 2)
  - Financial papers (Box 3-8)
  - Conferences, workshops, and projects; related organizations and programs (Box 9)
  - Anniversaries (Box 10)
  - Awards (Box 11)
  - Awards and photographs (Box 12)
  - Awards and correspondence (Box 13)
- Accession (2008-0104), 1988-1998, (2 boxes)
  Accession (2008-0104) (1.2 lin. ft.; 1988-1998) contains administrative files, including board of directors and executive group meeting minutes, periodic reports, financial information, and event planning information. Also included are copies of the WIA newsletter. Original folder titles were retained.
  - Women-In-Action (Box 1)
  - Elna B. Spaulding Founder's Award (Box 1)
  - To be filed (Box 1)
  - WIA newsletter (Box 1)
  - Minutes, board meetings (Box 1)
  - Clearinghouse reports (Box 1)
  - Membership rosters, committee rosters, hostess rosters (Box 2)
  - By-Laws (Box 2)
  - Duke Campus Ministry (Box 2)
  - Minutes, Executive Committee (Box 2)
  - Call for Action reports (Box 2)
  - Financial reports (Box 2)
  - United Way funding: WIA (Box 2)
  - Installation ceremony (Box 2)
  - Dinner programs, annual meetings (Box 2)
  - Clearinghouse volunteers (Box 2)
  - Women of Achievement, YWCA (Box 2)
  - Distinguished Women of North Carolina nominations (Box 2)
  - USB Key Volunteer nominations (Box 2)
  - Eula Harris Memorial (Box 2)
  - Parliamentary process, meeting management (Box 2)
  - Foundation applications (Box 2)
  - Vaudeville revisited, April 1987 (Box 2)
  - Anniversary dinner (Box 2)
  - Agency evaluation, United Way, 1988 (Box 2)
  - United Way agency relations (Box 2)